android.sc 2019-07-07

# Privacy Policy - Android News, Tips& Tricks, How To

## Privacy Policy for Android.sc

The Privacy Policy program of our visitors to Android Source (Android. sc) is very important to us.

At the Android Source website, the privacy of the visitor personal information is very important. During this page, is information on what type of personal data and information we receive and collect when you directly use or visit the Android.sc, and how the Android Source team safeguard your data/information.

The Android.sc website newer sell your personal information to third parties.

### Log Files

When a new visitor requests different pages from android. sc site, our Web-Server automatically recognizes the Browser Name (such as Internet Explorer,Chrome or Firefox), User IP (internet protocol) address, your device’s OS, Patch, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable),etc. All this information is collected solely for statistical purpose only and is not used in other ways to identify persons.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

As you might know, an HTTP cookie “cookie” is a small piece of information that is sent by a Web-Server to be stored on an individual Web-Browser (such as Internet Explorer,Chrome or Firefox) cache in plain text format. Every time when a visitor loads our website, the browser sends the stored cookie back to the web-server to notify the website of the visitor’s previous activity.

Also, the Android Source use cookie to store information, to record the user’s browsing activity such as personal preferences when you visit the android. sc site. This could include the slicing particulars buttons, logging in or recording which web pages were visited by the visitor as far back as weeks or months ago.

The Android Source website uses third party advertisements, some of these advertisers ( such as Google Ad sense program) may use different technology such as HTTP cookies and web beacons which will send the stored information, including the visitor IP address, ISP, the device OS name, the browser that the visitor used to visit the android.sc website, and in rare cases, whether you have Flash application installed.

We (Android Source Team) do not give any personally identifiable information, to advertisers as part of this collaboration.

Our advertisers use their own privacy policies, and the Android Source Team doesn’t have any access to this particular information.

### Collection and Use of Information

The Android Source website use tracking applications to recognize its users’ OS name, Browser Name and Version, visitor IP address, User ISP, etc. This information is collected and stored solely for statistical purposes and is not used to identify persons/ individuals.

If you have any supplementary questions regarding our Privacy Policy , please contact us via contact form.
